<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Services on Panaderos Services</title>
    <link>/services/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Services on Panaderos Services</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Feb 2018 11:52:18 +0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/services/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>API Integrations</title>
      <link>/services/api-integrations/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:15:34 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/services/api-integrations/</guid>
      <description>API INTEGRATIONS
Applications Programming Interfaces (APIs) are the connecting blocks between data clients and apps. These so called interfaces power the communication and sharing of data between various applications.
Business who are seeking innovative ways to address current business challenges in an effort to become more integrated and secured. APIs are one of the core components driving this change and should be a part of the business strategy.
APIs are not new, for decades application need an interface to communicate with each other.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Infrastructure &amp; Cloud</title>
      <link>/services/infrastructure-and-cloud/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:15:34 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/services/infrastructure-and-cloud/</guid>
      <description>INFRASTRUCTURE &amp;amp; CLOUD
Nowadays ICT environments have become unnecessary complex. In fact, complexity is regarded and widely accepted of any ICT department.
Cloud architecture is a very important area of concern. Cloud computing architecture refers to the components and other subcomponents that are required for cloud computing. These include the front end platform, back end platform, cloud-based delivery and a proper network. Combined with all these networks makes up the cloud computing architecture.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Security</title>
      <link>/services/security/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:15:34 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/services/security/</guid>
      <description>SECURITY
New EU Cybersecurity Strategy and new rules to make physical and digital critical entities more resilient.
Ever-increasing and complex threats require robust cybersecurity. Securing your network or ensuring the safety of your pharmaceutical line, for example, is very different to manning a perimeter. And today, with the shop floor no longer disconnected from the outside world and the IoT, it has never been more important to entrust your cybersecurity to experts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Software Development</title>
      <link>/services/software-development/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:15:34 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/services/software-development/</guid>
      <description>SOFTWARE DEVELOPMENT
We perform world-class custom software development services for startups, small-to-midsize (SMB), and enterprise-size businesses.
We are a mix of software experts and coding magicians, bound together by a shared passion for developing innovative solutions using the latest technologies and best practices in software development
Software architecture refers to the process of translating software characteristics into a structured solution that matches business and technical requirements. As a software development service provider, we leverage 25+ years of designing, db-structuring and programming and web applications for various markets using various technoligies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Strategy &amp; Audits</title>
      <link>/services/strategy-audits/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:15:34 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/services/strategy-audits/</guid>
      <description>POLICY, STRATEGY AND AUDIT
ICT is the fundamental backbone of any business that allows for potential growth and development in desired markets
It requires an ICT strategy that documents the business context, key initiatives, and strategic roadmap. To create a business-aligned ICT strategy, you must understand what the business does and what the business will need. Only then can a carefully thought-out, strategic and tactical plan be created for execution.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Web3 Innovation</title>
      <link>/services/web3-innovation/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:15:34 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/services/web3-innovation/</guid>
      <description>WEB3 INNOVATION
Distributed ledger technology (DLT) – generally referred to as blockchain – is picking up steam in terms of both enthusiasm and potential adoption
Blockchain and other have the potential to fundamentally transform a wide range of industries and to create new foundations for our economic and social systems.
Meanwhile, cryptocurrency is regarded a new dimension in the global economy many major corporations and venture capital firms are pouring money into Web 3.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
